Share cho ae tut kháng 792 2 hnay đang bấm rất giòn
Kháng = link 415 hoặc tab 415 ngay trong trình qlqc (Nút review account)
Thần chú:
My account has been disabled for payment due to recent travel and location change, I have fully verified my identity. I am sure this is a mistake of the Facebook automated system that led to my business coming to a halt. The epidemic, and the difficult economic situation, made my family in a very bad situation. My children suffered at the same time. I hope Facebook returns my account so I can run my family support business
Tích chọn dòng 2
Sau đó vào hòm thư spam luôn: Help me pls!
(via gì cũng đc, đổi ip bất kỳ nào # ip đang dùng là được để mà bấm nhé)
*****Cách 2:
TUT KHÁNG 792 CHO AE
LINK : https://www.facebook.com/help/contact/391647094929792
BƯỚC 1 : ae vào link 792 chọn tk , xong điền thần chú bên dưới , chõ chọn tệp ( ae vào chụp màn hình phần add thẻ đang bị đỏ tải lên ) xong chọn dòng 1 và bấm gửi , gửi xong nó hiện hộp thư thì ae bấm vào hộp thứ đợi 5p nó hiện thông báo về thì ae làm theo bước 2
✅ THẦN CHÚ : Dear Facebook Team, This is my card used to pay for facebook ads. I don't use this card to link with paypal. We are currently social distancing due to the covid 19 virus, so I can't give my bank statement. Attached photo is my card used to pay for facebook ads before. I believe it was a mistake. Please review my ad account and unblock my it so I can continue with my work. Thanks facebook
BƯỚC 2 : BẤM GỬI THẦN CHÚ SẼ CÓ TIN NHẮN VỀ HỘP THƯ , AE CHAT THÊM TRONG HỘP THƯ : do tôi đi du lịch nên bị bất thường
5P SAU SẼ VỀ
Mình đã thử và về sau vài tiếng.good luck ae!
Nguồn: Tổng hợp./r